[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6720bf8723801aa792c854b8"
  },
  "payloadId": "1730199431824",
  "clientApiKey": "R3AM-52JL-INUS-E5YL",
  "payloadPath": "/test",
  "payloads": [
    {
      "payloadName": "Payload1",
      "items": [
        {
          "index": 1,
          "question": "What is the difference between software engineering and computer science?",
          "answer": "Software engineering is the application of engineering principles to software development"
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "question": "Explain the difference between functional and object-oriented programming.",
          "answer": "Functional programming is a paradigm where computations are treated as mathematical functions, avoiding changing state and mutable data. It emphasizes immutability and pure functions. Object-oriented programming, on the other hand, organizes data as objects, which encapsulate data and behavior. It focuses on the interaction between objects and emphasizes concepts like inheritance, encapsulation, and polymorphism."
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "question": "What is the SOLID principle in object-oriented programming?",
          "answer": "SOLID is an acronym representing five design principles: Single Responsibility Principle (S), Open/Closed Principle (O), Liskov Substitution Principle (L), Interface Segregation Principle (I), and Dependency Inversion Principle (D). These principles guide developers to write maintainable, scalable, and robust object-oriented code. For example, the Single Responsibility Principle states that a class should have only one reason to change, promoting high cohesion and low coupling between classes."
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "question": "what is python?",
          "answer": "python is an programing Language used in the multiple applications such as Artificialinteligence, Datascience and Webpage applications "
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "payloadName": "Payload2",
      "items": [
        {
          "index": 1,
          "question": "What is the difference between software engineering and computer science?",
          "answer": "Software engineering is the application of engineering principles to software development"
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "question": "Explain the difference between functional and object-oriented programming.",
          "answer": "Functional programming is a paradigm where computations are treated as mathematical functions, avoiding changing state and mutable data. It emphasizes immutability and pure functions. Object-oriented programming, on the other hand, organizes data as objects, which encapsulate data and behavior. It focuses on the interaction between objects and emphasizes concepts like inheritance, encapsulation, and polymorphism."
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "question": "What is the SOLID principle in object-oriented programming?",
          "answer": "SOLID is an acronym representing five design principles: Single Responsibility Principle (S), Open/Closed Principle (O), Liskov Substitution Principle (L), Interface Segregation Principle (I), and Dependency Inversion Principle (D). These principles guide developers to write maintainable, scalable, and robust object-oriented code. For example, the Single Responsibility Principle states that a class should have only one reason to change, promoting high cohesion and low coupling between classes."
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "question": "what is python?",
          "answer": "python is an programing Language used in the multiple applications such as Artificialinteligence, Datascience and Webpage applications "
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "payloadName": "Payload3",
      "items": [
        {
          "index": 1,
          "question": "What is the difference between software engineering and computer science?",
          "answer": "Software engineering is the application of engineering principles to software development"
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "question": "Explain the difference between functional and object-oriented programming.",
          "answer": "Functional programming is a paradigm where computations are treated as mathematical functions, avoiding changing state and mutable data. It emphasizes immutability and pure functions. Object-oriented programming, on the other hand, organizes data as objects, which encapsulate data and behavior. It focuses on the interaction between objects and emphasizes concepts like inheritance, encapsulation, and polymorphism."
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "question": "What is the SOLID principle in object-oriented programming?",
          "answer": "SOLID is an acronym representing five design principles: Single Responsibility Principle (S), Open/Closed Principle (O), Liskov Substitution Principle (L), Interface Segregation Principle (I), and Dependency Inversion Principle (D). These principles guide developers to write maintainable, scalable, and robust object-oriented code. For example, the Single Responsibility Principle states that a class should have only one reason to change, promoting high cohesion and low coupling between classes."
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "question": "what is python?",
          "answer": "python is an programing Language used in the multiple applications such as Artificialinteligence, Datascience and Webpage applications "
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "payloadName": "Payload4",
      "items": [
        {
          "index": 1,
          "question": "What is the difference between software engineering and computer science?",
          "answer": "Software engineering is the application of engineering principles to software development"
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "question": "Explain the difference between functional and object-oriented programming.",
          "answer": "Functional programming is a paradigm where computations are treated as mathematical functions, avoiding changing state and mutable data. It emphasizes immutability and pure functions. Object-oriented programming, on the other hand, organizes data as objects, which encapsulate data and behavior. It focuses on the interaction between objects and emphasizes concepts like inheritance, encapsulation, and polymorphism."
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "question": "What is the SOLID principle in object-oriented programming?",
          "answer": "SOLID is an acronym representing five design principles: Single Responsibility Principle (S), Open/Closed Principle (O), Liskov Substitution Principle (L), Interface Segregation Principle (I), and Dependency Inversion Principle (D). These principles guide developers to write maintainable, scalable, and robust object-oriented code. For example, the Single Responsibility Principle states that a class should have only one reason to change, promoting high cohesion and low coupling between classes."
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "question": "what is python?",
          "answer": "python is an programing Language used in the multiple applications such as Artificialinteligence, Datascience and Webpage applications "
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}]